import { INTF_ExamsQ } from '../../Interface/Exams_Q/Exams_Q';

const Beginner: INTF_ExamsQ[] = [
    {
        exam_id: 1,
        question:
            'Which part of speech describes or gives more information about a noun?',
        options: ['Adjective', 'Adverb', 'Verb', 'Pronoun'],
        answer: 'Adjective',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 2,
        question:
            'Which of the following is the correct comparative form of "happy"?',
        options: ['happiester', 'happier', 'happyness', 'most happy'],
        answer: 'happier',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 3,
        question: 'Which article would you use before the word "apple"?',
        options: ['An', 'The', 'A', '0 article'],
        answer: '0 article',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 4,
        question:
            'What is the zero conditional sentence for the following statement: "If it rains, the ground gets wet."',
        options: [
            'If it rains, I will bring an umbrella.',
            'If it rains, the ground gets wet.',
            'If it rains, I go for a walk.',
            "If it rains, we'll have a picnic.",
        ],
        answer: 'If it rains, the ground gets wet.',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 5,
        question: 'Which future tense is used for making plans?',
        options: [
            'Future with will',
            'Future with going to',
            'Future with can',
            'Future with must',
        ],
        answer: 'Future with going to',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 6,
        question:
            'Which verb form is used after the verb "like" in the sentence "I like reading."?',
        options: [
            'Infinitive',
            'Gerund',
            'Past participle',
            'Present progressive',
        ],
        answer: 'Gerund',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 7,
        question:
            'Which verb form is used after the verb "want" in the sentence "I want to see my family."?',
        options: [
            'Infinitive',
            'Gerund',
            'Past participle',
            'Present progressive',
        ],
        answer: 'Infinitive',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 8,
        question: 'Which tense is used to talk about actions in the past?',
        options: [
            'Present perfect',
            'Past progressive',
            'Past simple',
            'Future perfect',
        ],
        answer: 'Past simple',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 9,
        question: 'What is the past simple form of the verb "go"?',
        options: ['went', 'goed', 'go', 'gone'],
        answer: 'went',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 10,
        question: 'Which modal verb is used to express abilities?',
        options: ['Can', 'Must', 'Should', 'Need'],
        answer: 'Can',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 11,
        question:
            'Which preposition is used to indicate a position between two objects?',
        options: ['On', 'Under', 'Between', 'Into'],
        answer: 'Between',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 12,
        question:
            'Which pronoun is used to refer to something that is far from both the speaker and the listener?',
        options: ['This', 'That', 'These', 'Those'],
        answer: 'Those',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 13,
        question:
            'Which verb form is used with the pronoun "I" in the present tense?',
        options: ['Am', 'Are', 'Is', 'Be'],
        answer: 'Am',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 14,
        question:
            'Which possessive pronoun is correct for the sentence "That book belongs to me."?',
        options: ['My', 'Your', 'His', 'Their'],
        answer: 'My',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 15,
        question:
            'Which present tense is used to talk about habits and daily routines?',
        options: [
            'Present simple',
            'Present progressive',
            'Present perfect',
            'Present continuous',
        ],
        answer: 'Present simple',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 16,
        question: 'Which adverb of frequency means "not ever"?',
        options: ['Always', 'Never', 'Seldom', 'Usually'],
        answer: 'Never',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 17,
        question:
            'Which verb form is used with "I" in the present perfect tense?',
        options: ['Have', 'Has', 'Had', 'Having'],
        answer: 'Have',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 18,
        question:
            'Which verb form is used with "you" in the present perfect tense?',
        options: ['Have', 'Has', 'Had', 'Having'],
        answer: 'Have',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 19,
        question:
            'Which verb form is used with "he" in the present perfect tense?',
        options: ['Have', 'Has', 'Had', 'Having'],
        answer: 'Has',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 20,
        question:
            'Which verb form is used with "they" in the present perfect tense?',
        options: ['Have', 'Has', 'Had', 'Having'],
        answer: 'Have',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 21,
        question:
            'Which verb form is used with "she" in the present perfect tense?',
        options: ['Have', 'Has', 'Had', 'Having'],
        answer: 'Has',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 22,
        question:
            'Which verb form is used with "it" in the present perfect tense?',
        options: ['Have', 'Has', 'Had', 'Having'],
        answer: 'Has',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 23,
        question:
            'Which verb form is used with "we" in the present perfect tense?',
        options: ['Have', 'Has', 'Had', 'Having'],
        answer: 'Have',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 24,
        question:
            'Which verb form is used with "you" (plural) in the present perfect tense?',
        options: ['Have', 'Has', 'Had', 'Having'],
        answer: 'Have',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 25,
        question:
            'Which verb form is used with "you" (singular) in the present perfect tense?',
        options: ['Have', 'Has', 'Had', 'Having'],
        answer: 'Has',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 26,
        question:
            'Which verb form is used with "I" in the imperative sentence?',
        options: ['Am', 'Are', 'Is', 'Be'],
        answer: 'Be',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 27,
        question:
            'Which verb form is used with "you" (singular) in the imperative sentence?',
        options: ['Am', 'Are', 'Is', 'Be'],
        answer: 'Be',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 28,
        question:
            'Which verb form is used with "he" in the imperative sentence?',
        options: ['Am', 'Are', 'Is', 'Be'],
        answer: 'Is',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 29,
        question:
            'Which verb form is used with "we" in the imperative sentence?',
        options: ['Am', 'Are', 'Is', 'Be'],
        answer: 'Are',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 30,
        question:
            'Which verb form is used with "they" in the imperative sentence?',
        options: ['Am', 'Are', 'Is', 'Be'],
        answer: 'Are',
    },
];

const PreIntermediate: INTF_ExamsQ[] = [
    {
        exam_id: 1,
        question: 'What is the adverb form of the adjective "quick"?',
        options: ['Quicker', 'Quickiest', 'Quickly', 'Quickful'],
        answer: 'Quickly',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 2,
        question: 'Which comparative form is correct for the adjective "old"?',
        options: ['Older', 'Oldest', 'More old', 'Most old'],
        answer: 'Older',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 3,
        question: 'What is the superlative form of the adjective "big"?',
        options: ['Bigger', 'Biggest', 'More big', 'Most big'],
        answer: 'Biggest',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 4,
        question:
            'Which word is an irregular adjective for the comparative form of "less"?',
        options: ['Lesser', 'Lesserest', 'More less', 'Most less'],
        answer: 'Lesser',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 5,
        question:
            'Which word is used to make a comparison in a sentence, like "She is a better driver than me."?',
        options: ['Than', 'As', 'Too', 'Only'],
        answer: 'Than',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 6,
        question: 'Which phrase is an adverbial phrase of time?',
        options: [
            'On the table',
            'Under the bed',
            'In the morning',
            'With my friend',
        ],
        answer: 'In the morning',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 7,
        question:
            'Which article is used before a countable noun that starts with a consonant sound?',
        options: ['A', 'An', 'The', 'No article'],
        answer: 'A',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 8,
        question:
            'Which article is used before a countable noun that starts with a vowel sound?',
        options: ['A', 'An', 'The', 'No article'],
        answer: 'An',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 9,
        question:
            'Which article is used before a countable noun when it is specific or known to the listener?',
        options: ['A', 'An', 'The', 'No article'],
        answer: 'The',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 10,
        question:
            'Which article is used before uncountable nouns or plural countable nouns to indicate a general or nonspecific reference?',
        options: ['A', 'An', 'The', 'No article'],
        answer: 'No article',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 11,
        question:
            'Which word is used to form the superlative degree of an adjective, like "He is the best man I have ever met."?',
        options: ['Best', 'Goodest', 'Excellenter', 'Greatiest'],
        answer: 'Best',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 12,
        question:
            'Which conditional is used for general truths or scientific facts?',
        options: [
            'Zero conditional',
            'First conditional',
            'Second conditional',
            'Third conditional',
        ],
        answer: 'Zero conditional',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 13,
        question:
            'Which conditional is used to talk about real or possible situations in the present or future?',
        options: [
            'Zero conditional',
            'First conditional',
            'Second conditional',
            'Third conditional',
        ],
        answer: 'First conditional',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 14,
        question:
            'Which conditional is used to talk about imaginary or unlikely situations in the present or future?',
        options: [
            'Zero conditional',
            'First conditional',
            'Second conditional',
            'Third conditional',
        ],
        answer: 'Second conditional',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 15,
        question:
            'Which word is used in the first conditional to express the condition?',
        options: ['If', 'Unless', 'When', 'Because'],
        answer: 'If',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 16,
        question:
            'Which word is used in the first conditional to express a negative condition?',
        options: ['If', 'Unless', 'When', 'Because'],
        answer: 'Unless',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 17,
        question:
            'Which conjunction is used to introduce a subordinate clause that specifies the place or location?',
        options: ['Where', 'When', 'Whose', 'Why'],
        answer: 'Where',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 18,
        question:
            'Which conjunction is used to introduce a subordinate clause that specifies the time?',
        options: ['Where', 'When', 'Whose', 'Why'],
        answer: 'When',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 19,
        question:
            'Which pronoun is used to introduce a subordinate clause that specifies possession?',
        options: ['Where', 'When', 'Whose', 'Why'],
        answer: 'Whose',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 20,
        question:
            'Which conjunction is used to introduce a subordinate clause that specifies the reason?',
        options: ['Where', 'When', 'Whose', 'Why'],
        answer: 'Why',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 21,
        question:
            'Which tense is used to express a sudden decision or intention?',
        options: [
            'Future with will',
            'Future with going to',
            'Present simple for future',
            'Present progressive for future',
        ],
        answer: 'Future with will',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 22,
        question:
            'Which tense is used to express a planned future action or prediction based on evidence?',
        options: [
            'Future with will',
            'Future with going to',
            'Present simple for future',
            'Present progressive for future',
        ],
        answer: 'Future with going to',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 23,
        question:
            'Which tense is used to express a scheduled future event or timetable?',
        options: [
            'Future with will',
            'Future with going to',
            'Present simple for future',
            'Present progressive for future',
        ],
        answer: 'Present simple for future',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 24,
        question:
            'Which tense is used to express future plans or arrangements?',
        options: [
            'Future with will',
            'Future with going to',
            'Present simple for future',
            'Present progressive for future',
        ],
        answer: 'Present progressive for future',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 25,
        question: 'Which modal verb is used to ask for help?',
        options: ['Can', 'Must', 'Shall', 'Should'],
        answer: 'Can',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 26,
        question: 'Which modal verb is used to make suggestions?',
        options: ['Can', 'Must', 'Shall', 'Should'],
        answer: 'Shall',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 27,
        question: 'Which modal verb is used to give advice?',
        options: ['Can', 'Must', 'Shall', 'Should'],
        answer: 'Should',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 28,
        question:
            'Which tense is used to talk about past actions or completed events?',
        options: [
            'Past simple',
            'Past progressive',
            'Present perfect',
            'Past perfect',
        ],
        answer: 'Past simple',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 29,
        question:
            'Which tense is used to talk about a past action that was in progress at a specific time?',
        options: [
            'Past simple',
            'Past progressive',
            'Present perfect',
            'Past perfect',
        ],
        answer: 'Past progressive',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 30,
        question:
            'Which tense is used to talk about an action that occurred before another past action?',
        options: [
            'Past simple',
            'Past progressive',
            'Present perfect',
            'Past perfect',
        ],
        answer: 'Past perfect',
    },
];

const Intermediate: INTF_ExamsQ[] = [
    {
        exam_id: 1,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the adjective: She was ____ by the horror movie.',
        options: ['bored', 'boring', 'tiring', 'tired'],
        answer: 'tired',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 2,
        question: "Which adverb means 'not at any time'?",
        options: ['Always', 'Never', 'Seldom', 'Sometimes'],
        answer: 'Never',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 3,
        question:
            "What is the correct word order for the adverb of frequency? 'I am never late.'",
        options: [
            'I never am late.',
            'Never am I late.',
            'I am never late.',
            'I am late never.',
        ],
        answer: 'I am never late.',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 4,
        question:
            "Choose the correct comparative and superlative form of the adjective: 'little'",
        options: [
            'little - less - least',
            'littler - less - least',
            'little - lesser - least',
            'little - less - lesser',
        ],
        answer: 'little - less - least',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 5,
        question:
            "Which phrase means 'having the same characteristics or qualities'?",
        options: ['Like', 'Alike', 'Slightly', 'Same as'],
        answer: 'Alike',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 6,
        question: "Choose the correct sentence using 'as... as':",
        options: [
            "He isn't as old as he looks.",
            "He isn't old as he looks.",
            "He isn't as old than he looks.",
            "He isn't old than he looks.",
        ],
        answer: "He isn't as old as he looks.",
    },
    {
        exam_id: 7,
        question: "Which word means 'similar in appearance or nature'?",
        options: ['Like', 'Alike', 'Slightly', 'Same as'],
        answer: 'Alike',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 8,
        question:
            'Which conditional is used to talk about general truths or scientific facts?',
        options: [
            '0 conditional',
            '1st conditional',
            '2nd conditional',
            '3rd conditional',
        ],
        answer: '0 conditional',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 9,
        question:
            'Which conditional is used to talk about real or possible situations in the present or future?',
        options: [
            '0 conditional',
            '1st conditional',
            '2nd conditional',
            '3rd conditional',
        ],
        answer: '1st conditional',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 10,
        question:
            'Which conditional is used to talk about imaginary or unlikely situations in the present or future?',
        options: [
            '0 conditional',
            '1st conditional',
            '2nd conditional',
            '3rd conditional',
        ],
        answer: '2nd conditional',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 11,
        question:
            'Which conditional is used to talk about imaginary or regretted situations in the past?',
        options: [
            '0 conditional',
            '1st conditional',
            '2nd conditional',
            '3rd conditional',
        ],
        answer: '3rd conditional',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 12,
        question:
            'Which conjunction is used to express cause and effect or contrast?',
        options: ['So', 'Which', 'Until', 'Why'],
        answer: 'So',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 13,
        question:
            'Which conjunction is used to express a period of time or duration?',
        options: ['So', 'Which', 'Until', 'Why'],
        answer: 'Until',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 14,
        question:
            'Which conjunction is used to introduce a reason or explanation?',
        options: ['So', 'Which', 'Until', 'Why'],
        answer: 'Why',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 15,
        question:
            'Which form is used to express a sudden decision or prediction?',
        options: ['Will', 'Future progressive', 'Going to', 'Passive voice'],
        answer: 'Will',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 16,
        question:
            'Which form is used to talk about an ongoing action in the future?',
        options: ['Will', 'Future progressive', 'Going to', 'Passive voice'],
        answer: 'Future progressive',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 17,
        question:
            'Which form is used to talk about plans and intentions in the future?',
        options: ['Will', 'Future progressive', 'Going to', 'Passive voice'],
        answer: 'Going to',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 18,
        question:
            'Which form is used to talk about the passive voice in the future?',
        options: ['Will', 'Future progressive', 'Going to', 'Passive voice'],
        answer: 'Passive voice',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 19,
        question: 'Which verbs are followed by the infinitive form?',
        options: [
            'Enjoy, mind, finish, suggest',
            'Want, hope, need, plan',
            'Stop',
            'Swim, talk',
        ],
        answer: 'Want, hope, need, plan',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 20,
        question: 'Which verbs are followed by the gerund form?',
        options: [
            'Enjoy, mind, finish, suggest',
            'Want, hope, need, plan',
            'Stop',
            'Swim, talk',
        ],
        answer: 'Enjoy, mind, finish, suggest',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 21,
        question:
            'Which verb can be followed by both the infinitive and gerund forms?',
        options: ['Enjoy', 'Mind', 'Finish', 'Suggest'],
        answer: 'Stop',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 22,
        question:
            "Which form is used to create a noun from a verb using '-ing'?",
        options: ['Infinitive', 'Gerund', 'Comparative', 'Superlative'],
        answer: 'Gerund',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 23,
        question: 'Which modal verb is used to express probability?',
        options: ['May', 'Can', 'Could', 'Must'],
        answer: 'May',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 24,
        question: 'Which modal verb is used for polite requests?',
        options: ['May', 'Can', 'Could', 'Must'],
        answer: 'May',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 25,
        question: 'Which modal verb is used to express ability in the past?',
        options: ['Can', 'Could', 'Must', 'Shall'],
        answer: 'Could',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 26,
        question: 'Which modal verb is used for polite requests?',
        options: ['May', 'Can', 'Could', 'Must'],
        answer: 'Can',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 27,
        question: 'Which modal verb is used to express probability?',
        options: ['May', 'Can', 'Could', 'Must'],
        answer: 'Can',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 28,
        question: 'Which modal verb is used to express ability?',
        options: ['Could', 'Must', 'Shall', 'May'],
        answer: 'Could',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 29,
        question: 'Which modal verb is used to express probability?',
        options: ['Could', 'Must', 'Shall', 'May'],
        answer: 'May',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 30,
        question: 'Which modal verb is used to express obligation?',
        options: ['Must', 'Need', 'Ought to', 'Shall'],
        answer: 'Must',
    },
];

const UpperIntermediate: INTF_ExamsQ[] = [
    {
        exam_id: 1,
        question: 'Which sentence is correct?',
        options: [
            'I am interesting in your offer.',
            'Your offer is interested.',
            'I am interested in your offer.',
            'Your offer is interesting.',
        ],
        answer: 'I am interested in your offer.',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 2,
        question: "Which adverb means 'not at any time'?",
        options: ['Always', 'Seldom', 'Sometimes', 'Never'],
        answer: 'Never',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 3,
        question: 'Choose the correct word order for the adverb of frequency.',
        options: [
            'I am never late.',
            'I never am late.',
            'I am late never.',
            'I late am never.',
        ],
        answer: 'I am never late.',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 4,
        question: "What is the superlative form of the adjective 'far'?",
        options: ['Farther', 'Farest', 'More far', 'Farthest'],
        answer: 'Farthest',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 5,
        question: 'Choose the correct sentence.',
        options: [
            'Laura gets the same salary than me.',
            'You’re just the same as your mother.',
            'Laura gets the same salary as me.',
            'You’re just same as your mother.',
        ],
        answer: 'Laura gets the same salary as me.',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 6,
        question: 'Choose the correct sentence.',
        options: [
            'He isn’t as old as he looks.',
            'He isn’t as old than he looks.',
            'He isn’t as old as he look.',
            'He isn’t as old than he look.',
        ],
        answer: 'He isn’t as old as he looks.',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 7,
        question: 'Choose the correct sentence.',
        options: [
            'You look like your mother.',
            'You look alike your mother.',
            'You look like your mother.',
            'You look alike your mother.',
        ],
        answer: 'You look like your mother.',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 8,
        question:
            'Which conditional is used for general truths or scientific facts?',
        options: [
            '0 conditional',
            '1st conditional',
            '2nd conditional',
            '3rd conditional',
        ],
        answer: '0 conditional',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 9,
        question: 'Complete the sentence: If it rains, ____ at home.',
        options: ['I stay', 'I will stay', 'I would stay', 'I stayed'],
        answer: 'I will stay',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 10,
        question: 'Complete the sentence: If I were you, ____ more water.',
        options: ['I will drink', 'I would drink', 'I drink', 'I drank'],
        answer: 'I would drink',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 11,
        question:
            'Complete the sentence: If I had married Paul, ____ that beautiful house.',
        options: [
            'I would live in',
            'I will live in',
            'I lived in',
            'I would have lived in',
        ],
        answer: 'I would have lived in',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 12,
        question:
            'Complete the sentence: If I had worked harder at school, ____ a better job now.',
        options: [
            'I would have',
            'I will have',
            'I would have had',
            'I will have had',
        ],
        answer: 'I would have',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 13,
        question: 'Choose the correct sentence.',
        options: [
            'I wish I am taller.',
            'I wish I was taller.',
            'I wish I were taller.',
            'I wish I will be taller.',
        ],
        answer: 'I wish I were taller.',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 14,
        question: 'Complete the sentence: I am sure she ____ the race.',
        options: ['wins', 'will win', 'win', 'is winning'],
        answer: 'will win',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 15,
        question:
            'Complete the sentence: I ____ my nephew to a concert tomorrow.',
        options: ['am taking', 'will take', 'take', 'took'],
        answer: 'will take',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 16,
        question: 'Complete the sentence: I ____ buy some books.',
        options: ['will go', 'am going to', 'go', 'went'],
        answer: 'am going to',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 17,
        question: 'Complete the sentence: I’m sure you ____ the test.',
        options: ['will pass', 'pass', 'would pass', 'are passing'],
        answer: 'will pass',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 18,
        question: 'Complete the sentence: I ____ living in a city eventually.',
        options: [
            'will get used to',
            'get used to',
            'would get used to',
            'got used to',
        ],
        answer: 'will get used to',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 19,
        question: 'Choose the correct sentence.',
        options: [
            'The dinner will cook by my friend.',
            'The dinner will be cooking by my friend.',
            'The dinner will be cooked by my friend.',
            'The dinner will cooked by my friend.',
        ],
        answer: 'The dinner will be cooked by my friend.',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 20,
        question: 'Choose the correct sentence.',
        options: [
            'She said she will come for sure.',
            'She said she would come for sure.',
            'She said she comes for sure.',
            'She said she is coming for sure.',
        ],
        answer: 'She said she would come for sure.',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 21,
        question:
            'Complete the sentence: Next year we ____ married for ten years.',
        options: ['will have been', 'have been', 'will have', 'have'],
        answer: 'will have been',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 22,
        question:
            'Complete the sentence: You ____ waiting for more than two hours when her plane finally arrives.',
        options: ['will have been', 'have been', 'will have', 'have'],
        answer: 'will have been',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 23,
        question: 'Choose the correct form: swim – ____',
        options: ['swam', 'swimming', 'swum', 'swumming'],
        answer: 'swimming',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 24,
        question: 'Choose the verb that is NOT followed by a gerund.',
        options: ['decide', 'make me', 'hate', 'prefer'],
        answer: 'make me',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 25,
        question: 'Choose the verb that is NOT followed by an infinitive.',
        options: ['think about', 'make me', 'hope', 'manage'],
        answer: 'make me',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 26,
        question: 'Choose the correct form: I’d rather ____',
        options: ['to stay', 'had better stay', 'stay', 'stayed'],
        answer: 'stay',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 27,
        question: "Choose the verb that is followed by 'to + gerund'.",
        options: ['help', 'look forward', 'avoid', 'enjoy'],
        answer: 'help',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 28,
        question: 'Complete the sentence: It ____ rain.',
        options: ['must', 'mustn’t', 'should', 'shouldn’t'],
        answer: 'must',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 29,
        question: 'Complete the sentence: You ____ smoke in the restaurant.',
        options: ['can', 'can’t', 'may', 'mustn’t'],
        answer: 'mustn’t',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 30,
        question: 'Complete the sentence: She ____ be very tired.',
        options: ['must', 'mustn’t', 'should', 'shouldn’t'],
        answer: 'must',
    },
];

const Confident: INTF_ExamsQ[] = [
    {
        exam_id: 1,
        question:
            "Choose the correct form of the adjective: This is the ____ book I've ever read.",
        options: ['good', 'better', 'best', 'well'],
        answer: 'best',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 2,
        question: 'Choose the correct adverb form: He speaks ____.',
        options: ['good', 'better', 'best', 'well'],
        answer: 'well',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 3,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the adjective: She is the ____ person in the class.',
        options: ['tall', 'taller', 'tallest', 'more tall'],
        answer: 'tallest',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 4,
        question: 'Choose the correct adverb form: The car drove ____.',
        options: ['fast', 'faster', 'fastest', 'more fast'],
        answer: 'fast',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 5,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the adjective: This is ____ day of my life.',
        options: ['bad', 'worse', 'worst', 'badly'],
        answer: 'worst',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 6,
        question: 'Choose the correct adverb form: She sings ____.',
        options: ['bad', 'worse', 'worst', 'badly'],
        answer: 'badly',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 7,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the adjective: The weather is getting ____.',
        options: ['hot', 'hotter', 'hottest', 'more hot'],
        answer: 'hotter',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 8,
        question: 'Choose the correct adverb form: They ran ____.',
        options: ['fast', 'faster', 'fastest', 'more fast'],
        answer: 'fast',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 9,
        question:
            "Choose the correct form of the adjective: This is the ____ movie I've ever seen.",
        options: ['boring', 'more boring', 'most boring', 'bored'],
        answer: 'most boring',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 10,
        question: 'Choose the correct adverb form: He studies ____.',
        options: ['hard', 'harder', 'hardest', 'more hard'],
        answer: 'hard',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 11,
        question:
            'Choose the correct modal verb: She ____ speak French fluently when she was young.',
        options: ['can', 'could', 'may', 'might'],
        answer: 'could',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 12,
        question:
            'Choose the correct modal verb: We ____ found the lost keys if we had searched more carefully.',
        options: ['can', 'could', 'may', 'might'],
        answer: 'could',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 13,
        question:
            'Choose the correct modal verb: You ____ have told me earlier!',
        options: ['can', 'could', 'may', 'should'],
        answer: 'should',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 14,
        question:
            "Choose the correct modal verb: I'm not sure, but he ____ have left already.",
        options: ['can', 'could', 'may', 'might'],
        answer: 'might',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 15,
        question:
            'Choose the correct modal verb: You ____ have finished the assignment by now.',
        options: ['can', 'could', 'may', 'should'],
        answer: 'should',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 16,
        question:
            "Choose the correct modal verb: I thought I ____ pass the exam, but I didn't study enough.",
        options: ['can', 'could', 'may', 'might'],
        answer: 'may',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 17,
        question:
            "Choose the correct modal verb: She ____ have seen the movie before, but she doesn't remember.",
        options: ['can', 'could', 'may', 'might'],
        answer: 'could',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 18,
        question:
            'Choose the correct modal verb: They ____ have arrived at the airport by now.',
        options: ['can', 'could', 'may', 'might'],
        answer: 'may',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 19,
        question:
            'Choose the correct modal verb: You ____ have asked for help if you were struggling.',
        options: ['can', 'could', 'may', 'should'],
        answer: 'should',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 20,
        question:
            'Choose the correct modal verb: He ____ have fixed the car by himself, but he decided to take it to the mechanic.',
        options: ['can', 'could', 'may', 'might'],
        answer: 'could',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 21,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the conditional sentence: If I ____ enough money, I would travel around the world.',
        options: ['have', 'had', 'will have', 'would have'],
        answer: 'had',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 22,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the conditional sentence: If you ____ a car, you could drive to work.',
        options: ['have', 'had', 'will have', 'would have'],
        answer: 'had',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 23,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the conditional sentence: If I ____ the answer, I would tell you.',
        options: ['know', 'knew', 'will know', 'would know'],
        answer: 'knew',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 24,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the conditional sentence: If she ____ hard, she will pass the exam.',
        options: ['work', 'worked', 'will work', 'would work'],
        answer: 'worked',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 25,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the conditional sentence: If they ____ to the party, they would have had a great time.',
        options: ['come', 'came', 'will come', 'would come'],
        answer: 'came',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 26,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the conditional sentence: If it ____ tomorrow, we will go for a picnic.',
        options: ['rain', 'rained', 'will rain', 'would rain'],
        answer: 'rained',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 27,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the conditional sentence: If he ____ the lottery, he would buy a new house.',
        options: ['win', 'won', 'will win', 'would win'],
        answer: 'won',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 28,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the conditional sentence: If we ____ the train, we would have been late.',
        options: ['miss', 'missed', 'will miss', 'would miss'],
        answer: 'missed',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 29,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the conditional sentence: If you ____ early, you will get a good seat.',
        options: ['arrive', 'arrived', 'will arrive', 'would arrive'],
        answer: 'arrived',
    },
    {
        exam_id: 30,
        question:
            'Choose the correct form of the conditional sentence: If they ____ hard, they would have succeeded.',
        options: ['work', 'worked', 'will work', 'would work'],
        answer: 'worked',
    },
];

export {
    Beginner,
    PreIntermediate,
    Intermediate,
    UpperIntermediate,
    Confident,
};
